<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Login (Additional) on AWS Android Social HoL</title>
    <link>/socialauth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Login (Additional) on AWS Android Social HoL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>kr-ko</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 08:30:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/socialauth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring Facebook OAuth</title>
      <link>/socialauth/facebook_config/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 08:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/socialauth/facebook_config/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we&amp;rsquo;re going to set up OAuth configurations on the Facebook developer site to support Facebook login.
In the lab, we will configure OAuth2.0 integration using the Hosted UI method provided by Amazon Cognito. With this method, we can implement social login without installing Facebook SDK.
 Create a developer account in Facebook developer portal. Log in to the Facebook developer site using own Facebook account. Select a &amp;lsquo;Create App&amp;rsquo; in &amp;lsquo;My Apps&amp;rsquo; menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring Amazon Cognito Service</title>
      <link>/socialauth/amplify-cognito/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 08:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/socialauth/amplify-cognito/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Cognito allows you to quickly and easily add user sign-up, sign-in, and access control to your mobile app.
Run the following command from the top level of your Android project.
amplify auth update  Please refer to the picture below for the selection in progress.
When setting the domain name, names including aws, amazon, cognito, and _ cannot be used. You should enter the name in the form of &amp;lsquo;android-workshop&amp;rsquo; + &amp;lsquo;random text&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing social login</title>
      <link>/socialauth/facebook_login/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 08:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/socialauth/facebook_login/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will implement Facebook-based social login using Cognito&amp;rsquo;s Hosted UI feature.
With Hosted UI feature, OAuth2 authentication is done between servers, so we do not need to install a mobile SDK provided by Facebook. Currently, supporting Identity Providers are Facebook, Google, and Amazon.
Copy the code below to complete the _ openFacebookLogin method for adding Hosted UI functionality for Facebook login.
// AuthMainActivity.java public class AuthMainActivity extends AppCompatActivity { .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>